foreign
[Music]
today I wanted to share something that's
been on my mind recently
but to preface it I grew up without
social media I had an account at one
point as a teenager but I rarely used it
last year was when I first became
consistently active on social media and
it has been a wonderful way to connect
with other artists and all of you
and I can say for certain that the
stories and messages you've shared have
enriched my life
I've enjoyed it very much but have also
observed how easy it is for social media
to fuel a sense of inadequacy and
comparison
as someone who hasn't been exposed to it
for very much until now I see how
powerful it can be and cannot imagine
the influence it has over people who've
had it all their lives
[Music]
it is so easy to see what someone shares
especially their lifestyle as something
you wish you had
but in my case that feeling never went
away by moving over here
when I was in the city I romanticized
country living and then when I moved
leaving my community and my friends I
started to romanticize City living out
here there aren't very many people and
so while it is still very possible to
make friends who share your interests
it's not as easy as in the city with
hundreds of thousands of people
there are a few restaurants shops and to
get to large stores you need to take a
two hour round trip
initially while living here I missed my
book clubs my co-workers and had a
horrible sense that I was missing out on
Life by living in such a quiet area
I kept thinking I'm So Young why am I
not traveling the world and doing
exciting things
I'd see photos of my friends online
going out to restaurants and taking
vacations to other places and I felt
like I was horribly boring I was just
working all the time on minimum wage and
trying to afford my health insurance if
you live in America you know what I mean
well that has now changed and I finally
feel financially secure
for a long time I still wondered about
the careers and opportunities I may have
had in the city
foreign
past jobs it was easy to compare myself
to friends who were able to afford
things easier and had jobs that I
thought were maybe more impressive
when my income increased I felt more at
ease in some areas but I still didn't
feel any more satisfied with my life
foreign
[Music]
of course I do not blame social media
for making me insecure exposure to it
still made me regularly question my own
happiness and satisfaction with life
especially when online everyone else
seems happier than you
they brought up insecurities that I've
never experienced before this year I
quickly realized how important it was to
only be involved in online communities
that add True Value education or Inspire
my creativity
I also found that with social media it
is easy to project your own
dissatisfaction or insecurity on other
people instead of empowering yourself to
embrace who you are and that everyone's
timeline is different
As I Grew to understand myself better I
realized that I was preoccupied with
comparison and judging other Lifestyles
simply by the highlights I saw online
instead of really asking myself would
that life suit me would that lifestyle
help me help other people and leave the
world a better place
foreign
towards my goals accepting that I may
not get instant gratification
if I hadn't been able to move to the
countryside when I did I'm confident I
could be just as happy in the city
embracing the chapters of my story and
slowly but surely working towards my
dreams and gaining a lot of experience
along the way
[Music]
that leads me to talk about this Channel
and the aspects of life I choose to
highlight here
as you can see I share for the most part
happy your thoughtful days that are full
of peace and calm
but I have bad lazy hectic days all the
time I'm not who I want to be every day
and I fall short a lot and I can be very
self-critical Sometimes I Cry and I
actually I I cry a lot those are usually
very private moments and when I'm upset
I spend time with someone I love like my
boyfriend and it would seem very strange
to pull out a camera and start filming
those very raw moments while keeping
them authentic mostly because I want
this channel to be about inspiration and
ideas and peace and art not my own daily
struggles
it is also very important to me to not
force other people to be part of my
videos if it makes them uncomfortable
that is why I don't share everything
because when I'm with someone or
experiencing a very special moment I
want to experience it fully
pausing to capture it for posterity
would detract from that instead I know
that the only way I will keep being
inspired to make videos is to make them
when motivated and enjoy my life
but how I like to communicate those hard
moments is through my words where I try
to share a more intimate reality that's
what makes me comfortable and keeps me
inspired I suppose I hope that makes
sense
[Music]
anyway I appreciate all of you I really
do and I hope you're doing well and
embracing whatever chapter of your story
you're currently in each one is precious
and has so much to give I really believe
there is so much love and beauty in this
messy World everyone is different and
moving at their own pace
take care and have a lovely day or night
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]